ash here
you know i saved jesse's life once am i
supposed to be thankful for that
do my eyes deceive me or are you wearing
skates you'll see what these could do
nice skates very cute you gonna swap
those out before we get to the gun
fight you'll see what these could do
y'all our teammates wearing skates to a
gunfight
you'll see what these could do
brave are you to show your face around
here jesse
well i know how much you missed me still
have a picture of me at the hideout i
hear
on the dart board bet you look at it
every day
flattering really real nice bike you got
ash what'd you do with it jesse
parked it somewhere i'm damned if i
remember where i left the keys though
ash how about we let bygones be bygones
oh you know that's not the way it works
jesse
i was hoping you'd make an exception for
old time's sake
and how's bob he's just fine
thank you for your concern
still remember your old house gotta miss
that old sofa
it was a shae's lounge it was a foot
rest
you always were the ambitious one ash
you make that sound like a bad thing
you'd still be on a farm if it weren't
for me
some days that doesn't sound so bad
you know you never were my type ash
too competent too rich
stay behind me i will keep you safe yeah
thanks but i already have a bodyguard
that's a lot of armor though i guess you
are a pretty big
target i guess i
am
you still have any contacts with los
muertos
i might what's in it for me i'd offer
you money
but i don't think that's what you're
after no
so any good stories about the cowboy
oh with a grumpy dwarf in a halloween
costume on our side how can we lose
watch it cowless
that rifle's a fine piece of work looks
a little unwieldy though
perhaps in the hands of an amateur
it's always gonna be this way
now who's the better shot there's only
one way you get to leave the gang
you need to learn the rules
see you space cowboy
squid needs more seasoning
thank you